



# ABDHI NEGRIANSYAH SYUHADA

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER / JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER / JUNIOR BACK-END DEVELOPER

#### **CONTACT**

(+62)857-6152-4700



abdhins29@gmail.com



abdhins29.github.io



Komplek Perumahan Lubuk Intan Blok E No. 5, Kota Padang, Sumatera Barat, 25173

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2019, Universitas Putra Indonesia YPTK Padang, Information System.

Bachelor Degree GPA of 3.22



## **CERTIFICATE**

Oct 2019 - Oct 2022, Dicoding Academy. Dasar Pemrograman Web

## **SKILL**

- Codeigniter
- PHP
- HTML
- AJAX
- Javascript
- Javascrip
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- MySQL

- Teamwork
- · Problem Solving
- Discipline
- Leadership
- Management Risk
- Responsible

## **SOCIAL MEDIA**



linkedin.com/in/abdhins



facebook.com/abdhins



twitter.com/abdhins

#### **ABOUT ME**

Hi! My name is Abdhi. I'm 23 years old. I work as a Freelancer Web Aplication less than 1 year experience with specializing PHP Programming Language and MySQL Database for college students. I work as a Digital Activator and Team Leader Community Promotion less than 3 months for company.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

08 Jul 2020 - Now, PT. Riau Sakti United Plantation, Programmer.

System analysis to be made, system development that has been analyzed into a website and performs system maintenance.

27 Jan 2020 - 15 Feb 2020, PT. Mitra Media Citra, Team Leader Community Promotion.

- Finding and notify new users that PT. HM.
  Sampoerna Tbk. already have a mobile-based application that is "AYO SRC".
- Inform the new user that the application "AYO SRC", users are permitted to shop at the stalls SRC provided throughout Indonesia.
- Inform the new user that the application "AYO SRC", users can also get updated information about what is happening in Indonesia.
- Achieving the target of new users that have been defined by PT. HM. Sampoerna Tbk. Cab. Padang.

02 Nov 2019 - 02 Dec 2019, PT. HM. Sampoerna Tbk. Cab. Padang, Digital Activator.

- Create an inspiring team environment with an open communication culture.
- Set clear team goals. Delegate tasks and set deadlines.
- Oversee day-to-day operation.
- Monitor team performance and report on metrics.
- Motivate team members.
- Discover training needs and provide coaching. Listen to team members' feedback and resolve any issues or conflicts.
- Recognize high performance and reward accomplishments.

Jan 2019 – Dec 2019, Universitas Putra Indonesia YPTK Padang, Freelancer Web Developer.

Help making a website project information system, such as:

- Pharmacy Drug Data Processing
- University Alumni Tracking
- Reservations and Promotion of Animal Hospital
- Car Rental
- Admission Junior High School
- Saving and loan Cooperative